Blue Cop's Special Training!
Blue Cop!
How about you ditch this piece of scrap metal,
and form a new team with me, Jun?
Alright! Heeheehee!
H-Huh?!
Wait Jun!
Please! Don't leave me!
Jun!!
What are you talking about?
I'm not going anywhere.
You even had a nightmare...
the defeat must have come as a shock.
Lighten up, Blue Cop!
Next time, you'll definitely defeat that guy in one blow!
With my current strength... There's no way I can beat Wild Guardy.
Don't doubt yourself like that!
We'll work hard together to become even stronger!
Become stronger?
So it's time for some special training?
Special training?
Yes. Just leave it to me.
Ok!
Special training for Blue Cop?
Yeah. Uncle Edo said he's going to set up a new spot for some special training. He's been working on some new equipment for it.
Really? Wow! I wanna come check it out!
I heard it will be ready today. Should I ask?
Blue Cop!
Jun.
Is the special training ready?
Yeah.
-It's almost done. We'll be starting the training soon.
-No, no. That goes over here!
Alright! Keep it up! I'll be there soon.
What are you guys so excited about?
Waaah!!
U-Uh, it's nothing...
...hey guys...
Jun, did you forget Crest invited us to his house today?
Aha... I kinda did...
You're not trying to skip out on it, are you?
Actually, I do have something, uh...
Pretending to be busy, huh?
If it's nothing urgent, why don't you just drop by for a little while?
You said you wanted to try out the latest VR game.
Uh... If that's alright?...
Of course, come on.
Let's go.
This will be fun!
Woah...
This place is huge!
Welcome back, master.
You have a robot at home?!
His name is Sebastian.
Pleasure to meet you all.
He's an all-purpose robot. He can do everything from chores to security.
And your parents?
They're often overseas for work.
So, Crest... you live here all by yourself?
Well, yes... but it doesn't get lonely.
After all, I've made so many new friends around here.
I-I'm happy for you.
Ah!
This is the last one.
Alright, we're finally ready now!
Huh? What are you going to do with these sticks?
You'll find out soon.
Blue Cop! To the center, please!
Yes, sir!
Huh?
Is this good?
Yep.
Alright, then!..
Woah...
This training module will teach you how to dodge enemy attacks and to land counterattacks.
I made it by modifying a virtual hologram game.
But it's synced to your neural network, so it will still pack a punch if you get hit.
Alright, are you ready?
Of course.
Here we go!
That looked like it hurt.
The effects are stronger than expected.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's go again!
No chance, kid!
Haha! Way to go, Vance! Yeah!
Get him, Theo!
Haha, you'll never beat me!
Jun. Want to give it a go?
Alright!
I'll make sure to avenge Theo.
Not you... or you...
Aha! I'll pick this one!
Will this training even work for mechanical lifeforms like us?
Hard to say. Looks like a waste of time.
It's not a waste of time! Hard work and perseverance always pays off!
Again!
Haha! No matter how many times you try, I'll still kick your butt!
That was just a warm up! I'll beat you this time!
Alright! I'll beat you until you collapse from exhaustion!
Ugh. What are they getting so worked up over?
At least they're having fun.
How ya like this?!
Again!
Grr... Again!
That's enough "agains" for now. Go take a break.
Let me show you how it's done!
Alright.
Alright, let's go!
I wasn't ready!
Come on!
Seems like he's still not ready.
Haha! He's running into every hit! That's got to be some kind of world record!
If you calculate the course and speed of the attack-
and respond a little before it lands...
H-hey! Wait up! Augh...
Ugh. This isn't helping at all.
No. I think I've figured it out.
Edo! Let's try one more time.
Attack pattern?
Mhm. Each robot character has its own attack pattern and timing.
Figure that out and you might be able to beat Vance.
Heh! No amount of advice is gonna help this loser beat me!
Alright. Thanks.
Again!
It's working!
I can get stronger!
Well done! Just do as I showed you!
I think the trick is to do the opposite of what you did.
Seems like Blue Cop's reaction time has picked up!
Looks like he's predicting the attack pattern and moving preemptively.
Hey! Why aren't the hits landing?!
Grr... so that's how you wanna play?
It's about time I get to use this!
Huh? Hey...
How did you get so big?!
Get ready for my special move!
Never!
Never!-
Give up!
Huh?
What is...
This power?...
Jun!
Blue Cop!
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
Aw, come on!
What was all that about?! Probably just dumb luck!
Hey Jun. Could I have your watch?
Augh?!
Of course, I'm not expecting it for free.
I'll trade you anything in this room for it.
How about it?
For real?
Then can I have your TV?
Can I have your robot?
W-what are you talking about?
That could be something important to Jun.
It's up to Jun to decide if he wants to trade.
So... what would you like?
Uhh...
Sorry! I have to go now!
T-Thanks for the game!
And so... he just runs away.
Blue Cop!
Jun!
I get it now! When our hearts join as one, we become stronger!
So it's true. The voice from before... it was you.
It seems like the Metal Breath still holds a lot of secrets to be discovered.
Hm.
So when Jun and Blue Cop's feelings are connected, the power of his card grows...
and new skills are unleashed.
Then... that means we could also power up like Blue Cop.
Alright! Let's start training together!
It could be Wild Guardy or Heavy Iron... we can beat 'em all!
Let's do it, guys!
But... where's Uncle Edo?
My storage room...!
I really thought I had him right where I wanted.
But I didn't manage to get the Metal Breath.
I'm sorry, Wild Guardy.
You do not have to apologize.
The great Wild Guardy will take the Metal Breath with my own skill and prowess.